[{"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "Did he have a point?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "You know, I know what all the buttons of an airplane do.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Is he right as an elected official to stick rigidly to those parameters or not?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Slightly.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "And for the wider country, by the weekend, is everything beginning to get back to some kind of normality?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "I was actually listening to it here in San Antonio through the live feed that they provide and when he said that I was like -- I must have heard that wrong and realized I hadn't heard it wrong and this is the sense of this particular senator takes over and over and over again.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "... what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Well, it makes my heart pound for -- to hear that.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "What do you feel about this?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "What do you think can be done to try and change that mentality?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Well, criticism, I couldn't even go beyond criticism.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "What is your specific criticism of what they are doing in Denmark?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Is that the only way to try and control groups of animals in the wild or in the zoo?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "But is that any argument that has any wanted to you at all about the way you control a group of perhaps predominantly male and female giraffe in that situation?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Well, I think you're raising a good point.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Why should the Danish frankly be able to treat giraffe's the way they wish too if they believe it's the right way to treat them?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I would say, in the older days obviously we had our problems.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "From your expertise, is that I am right, are certain animals able to deal with being in zoos better than others and should there be restrictions dependent on that?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "I didn't even know.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "What the hell is going through your mind?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I mean is -- I still enjoy doing it.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "I would imagine the pleasure factor diminishes quite quickly, isn't it?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Not everyday is like that obviously, but it's just the whole another world you're just by yourself, I mean, just you and the machine and you're trying everything not to get stuck and just keep your thrill way up.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "What makes you guys go out there and risk death?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Well, like -- I've seen a little bit of like what I thought was a rooster from another snowmobile.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Did you think you are going to survived it or what happens to you in your head?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I mean -- and there is a -- to a certain extent a form regulation like there's areas we can't go.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "But do you think on serious point there should be some form of regulations for snowmobiling?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "I mean there's a lot of different of styles of it I guess.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Do you basically have to have a screw loose to be doing this snowmobiling a lot?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Yes, and there's way crazier people than me.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "So that's a yes basically, isn't it?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "It doesn't feel surreal I mean it feels very real it's happening, and I understand what's happening, I'm aware of what's happening.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "How do you feel about this extraordinary resurgence?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "I think it's a wonderful moment in my career that is in the middle of its approach.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Is that the culmination of everything you've ever work for or do you believe in a way it maybe the start of something very special?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "I tweeted the other day, are you on Twitter?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "That's -- yeah.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Is that the key?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Well, I've got thanks -- I've got my own personal thanks to God, I've got my own personal thanks to family in many respects, the family I've got now, the family I came from, and I've got another little secret thank for somebody I know very well that I might share if I was so fortunate to.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Who are the key people when you look back over the whole time that you would feel most thankful to?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not -- I'm -- look, I'm not there yet so ...", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "What do you think you'll feel when you're standing there if you get that?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "... I really haven't thought about what I would feel.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "But if you do, how would you feel?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Any moment.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Replay that -- just any moment?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "One you'd most like to live through again.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "The greatest moment?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "Courage, integrity, you know, anybody loses a father that's the main crutch in a man's life, and he's there for a reason because, you know, if it ever comes down to it you got, you know, my father would lean up against me.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "What impact did that have on you?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "He'd love it.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "So what's your father have made of you being Oscar nominee?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Can you quite believe it?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Go to Mexico and drink the water.", "docId": "140213pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "How I can lose 43 pounds quickly?", "qSentId": 519}]